allwebco-templates.com 2018-09-28

# Allwebco Design Corporation Privacy Policy

Allwebco Design Corporation is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect any personal information you provide online: It is our policy that your personal information, such as your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number are private and kept confidential. This information is used only to process your order or to reply directly to any queries you may have about our products. 

**Allwebco will never provide or sell any personal information to third parties.**

## Payment Security

All online transactions through our website are handled with industry-standard SSL encryption through the Paypal and 2CO payment gateways. Secure SSL means that when you enter your credit card number into our secure order form and press the purchase button, your information goes through a secure encryption process. This prevents any person on the Internet from seeing any information you submit. Your payment is authorized without human intervention. 

## Cookies

The allwebcodesign.com website does not set any cookies that are stored on your device, however, some 3rd party scripts that we do use on our website, such as Google Analytics, Google AdSense and Google Plus, do use cookies and may store information, through the use of cookies, in your web browser. No other 3rd party vendor, other than Google, uses cookies on our website. 

## About the Google Ads in Some Templates

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. Google uses the "Doubleclick" Cookie though ads posted on allwebcodesign.com, which tracks use of allwebcodesign.com and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer. 

You may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated?hl=en). Then see: Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. You can find the [AdSense Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) here. 

Allwebco Design Corporation is not a subsidiary of, or affiliated with Google Inc. other than using their AdSense program for advertisements. All Google ad content and cookies are controlled by and served by Google. 

|    

  * Included features
  * Use any HTML or text editor
  * Works with many [free editors](http://www.allwebco-templates.com/support/S_HTML_software.htm)
  * Javascripts and features built-in
  * Replaceable .jpg and .gif images
  * Basic HTML designs
  * Flash headers
  * Graphic logo option built-in
  * Edit all Flash with a text editor
  * All "linked" Flash images
  * No special software needed
  * All source files included
  * Plain text customizable menus
  * Order with or without [hosting](http://allwebco.com/)
  * No monthly fees
  * Everything you need in one place
  * F.A.Q.

Click here to get started now  

No monthly fees  
No special software required  
  
---|---
